

Web Developer located in Milwaukee, WI with a demonstrated history of 5+ years working in the digital space. Skilled in Email Development, Front-end Development, and Cascading Style Sheets (CSS, SCSS). Working towards a full-stack role focused on C#. Strong engineering professional with a B.A. Art focused in Graphic Design from UW-Whitewater.

262.993.0947 becktj07@uww.edu

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# becktj07.github.io

## Bader-Rutter

Jr. Developer

Milwaukee, WI April 2018 - Present

I started as a dedicated email developer for Corteva Agrisciene and Zoetis. I now work on landing pages in Oracle's Eloqua platform, and on two large .NET based websites, **Mycogen.com** and **Phytogen.com** respectively.

#### **MATC Milwaukee**

Student

Milwaukee, WI Jaunary 2018 - May 2018

After an extended job search, I went back to school full-time. I focused on server-side development with C#. Courses included:

- · Intro C#
- · SQL Server
- · Intermediate C#
- · Javascript Frameworks
- · .NET Core w/ Entity Framework (currently enrolled)

### **Ascedia**

Associate Interface Developer

Milwaukee, WI October 2014 - August 2017

I collaborated with application developers and designers, and brought static design concepts to reality. Client work ranged from large scale, custom builds, to maintenance tasks in versions of Kentico CMS and Wordpress.

#### Notable Work:

- Milwaukee County Transit System www.ridemcts.com
- Cubic Designs www.cubicdesigns.com
- Davalid Ridge Hop Farm www.davaliridge.com
- Untitled Creative Studio www.untitledcreativestudio.com

# The LANG Companies

Web Designer

Pewaukee, WI August 2013 - Oct 2014

I designed and coded html emails, managed email campaigns, and in-house front end development. I managed product pages and web content for www.lang.com, a site built on Magento e-commerce CMS.

#### **EDUCATION**

University of Wisconsin-Whitewater Mukwonago High School

BA Art - Graphic Design Cum Laude, May 2013

Class of 2008